<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>What does ~rogbeer put here?</title>
 <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/"/>
 <updated>2018-10-09T08:29:23+00:00</updated>
 <id>http://tilde.town</id>
 <author>
   <name>Tony Chen</name>
   <email>phtan90@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Places where I have used my laptop</title>
   <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/2018/10/08/overcast/"/>
   <updated>2018-10-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://tilde.town/2018/10/08/overcast</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have had the luxury and privilege of using my laptop at 
the following places, where beverages are sold&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I am currently residing in Singapore - which is in South-east Asia, if you
are not familiar with her.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Brunches’. URL: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/BrunchesCafe/&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/BrunchesCafe/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Enchanted’. URL: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/EnchantedCafeSg/&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/EnchantedCafeSg/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Old Hen’. URL: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/oldhencoffee/&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/oldhencoffee/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Coffeesmith’. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/CoffeesmithSG/&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/CoffeesmithSG/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Kopi &amp;amp; Tarts’, in the shopping mall City Square. &lt;a href=&quot;https://kopiandtarts.com.sg/&quot;&gt;https://kopiandtarts.com.sg/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;‘Real Food’, in the shopping mall Orchard Central. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.realfoodgrocer.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.realfoodgrocer.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had the inspiration to post about this after visiting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.taniarascia.com/&quot;&gt;Tania Rascia&lt;/a&gt;’s
record of cafes that she has visited: &lt;a href=&quot;https://taniarascia.github.io/coffee/&quot;&gt;https://taniarascia.github.io/coffee/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course I can only have such inspiration if &lt;a href=&quot;http://phtan.github.io/religion.html&quot;&gt;my god&lt;/a&gt;
 gives it to me.
I thank Him for that.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A room-mate leaves</title>
   <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/2018/10/08/indoors-and-windowless/"/>
   <updated>2018-10-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://tilde.town/2018/10/08/indoors-and-windowless</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One of my room-mates - who has just moved in, in the past two weeks or so - 
said he is leaving tomorrow to reside at his new work-place, a ‘vegetable farm’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, he said he would be staying on the farm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And he says that ‘in the beginning’, he would have no pay/salary. Perhaps he
would have food and accommodation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I asked him for the name of the place, he said it is called ‘Onesimus Garden’,
which he claims is in the area of Lim Chu Kang (probably in the north-west region
of the island of Singapore).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Setting this up with Jekyll</title>
   <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/2018/10/04/jekyll/"/>
   <updated>2018-10-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://tilde.town/2018/10/04/jekyll</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I thought I would post about the resources that I have had the privilege to
refer to, in trying out the static-site generator Jekyll and one of the themes
for it, Poole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;resources&quot;&gt;Resources&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In no particular order,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lande, J. (2014). ‘How I Created a Beautiful and Minimal Blog Using Jekyll, Github Pages, and poole’. URL: &lt;a href=&quot;http://joshualande.com/jekyll-github-pages-poole&quot;&gt;http://joshualande.com/jekyll-github-pages-poole&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed URL on 4th Oct 2018.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tilde.town/~resir014&quot;&gt;Resi&lt;/a&gt;. (2016). ‘Jekyll and tilde.town’. In &lt;em&gt;tilde.town&lt;/em&gt; (Issue 2), pp. 5 to 9. URL: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/tildetown/zine/blob/master/issue_2/zine.pdf&quot;&gt;https://github.com/tildetown/zine/blob/master/issue_2/zine.pdf&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed URL on 4th OCt 2018.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Moore, P. (2014). ‘Clearing Up Confusion Around baseurl – Again’. URL: &lt;a href=&quot;https://byparker.com/blog/2014/clearing-up-confusion-around-baseurl/&quot;&gt;https://byparker.com/blog/2014/clearing-up-confusion-around-baseurl/&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed URL on 4th Oct 2018.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A new way? nineteenth of March 2018: Night</title>
   <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/2018/03/19/night/"/>
   <updated>2018-03-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://tilde.town/2018/03/19/night</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When did it become an assumption that I have to have a password on the 
Internet or even my desktop-computer? I was inspired to think if 
something has gone wrong, in the design of Internet-and-computer 
technologies, when I realised that an engineering problem - how to 
display certain information on a web-site - could possibly be solved by 
letting users run commands on the server (as opposed as viewing data on 
a client) Passwords, levels of privilege, ‘admininistrator-rights’ - 
don’t all these scream ‘I don’t trust you. I don’t trust others’ Now is 
that what I want in my life, I ask. Do I want to indirectly say ‘I don’t 
trust others’ every time I use a technology. Or do I want to spend time 
building (trust in) relationships that arguably are made and broken by 
(mutual) trust. Does using technology necessarily mean that I have to 
give up on trust and/or trust-building. Is it possible we could find a 
new way to use technology so that we find the satisfaction (and 
intimacy) that comes from a rewarding relationship with a something. A 
god. A business-partner. So on and so forth.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>fifteenth of March 2018: Sunny</title>
   <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/2018/03/15/sunny/"/>
   <updated>2018-03-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://tilde.town/2018/03/15/sunny</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>10th November 2016: Rainy</title>
   <link href="http://tilde.town/~rogbeer/2016/11/10/rainy/"/>
   <updated>2016-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://tilde.town/2016/11/10/rainy</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’m suffering. They are suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to put an end to suffering? For myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Others can try out my methods if they want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course they have to find out their own way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kodo Suzuki Roshi said that adults have to become like children, and children have to become like adults,
for children to grow. Apparently, he said that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I were a foster parent of all these lovable children in the world, my impending death is something
I have to deal with. Preparations have to be made for other people to help all these children grow,
so that my death will not stop their growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, as Jobs said, death means having to tell your children what you thought you would
have the rest of your life so tell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THere is a temple called Antaiji in Japan. The people there practice zazen that is good for nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a person who is helping people to find a suitable livelihood. She also practises Zen. Her
book is a work-in-progress. It is predicted to be published in Fall 2017. Her name is Maia Duerr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are people who teach Zen in Singapore. Their names are Vivienne and Boey Wah Keong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will do what I amy not have the time to do. At least, they can do what I may run out of time to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zazen is good for nothing. It is the way to liberate-save suffering people-human. Suzuki Roshi 
said that.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
